getautocar.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy | New and used Car Buying Guide with Car Reviews, Pictures, And Auto insurance ,Auto loans,Car Finance Advice.

Privacy Statement

We _**NEVER**_ sell or furnish information to third parties unless instructed to do so by the person who gave the information. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site. If you have any questions about the privacy and security at our website, you can send email to us :admin@getautocar.com

Information Collection and Use  
We are the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website. We request information from the user on our forms. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and address) some forms may require personal information. This information is used for the stated purposes and to fill customers request. If we have trouble processing a customers request, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the users hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site.

Log Files  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing  
**Any information that is shared with other companies to complete the customers request is not retain, share, stored or used for any secondary purposes by these companies.

**Links  
**Our web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

**Newsletter  
**If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address.

**Security  
**All data is protected using the most advanced methods available. We take every precaution to protect our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When a form asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just browsing.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must reenter their password to regain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

Un-Subscribe – Correct/Update  
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive mail list messages.
